<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Features>
    <Header>
        This file is used to track features being considered for development.
    </Header>
    <Feature name="Backtester">
        <Added>2 April 2012</Added>
        <UserStory>
            As a user, I can back test a trading strategy to determine which transactions would have been generated by the strategy.
        </UserStory>
    </Feature>
    <Feature name="Correlated Funds">
        <Added>23 March 2012</Added>
        <UserStory>
            As a user, I can find which ticker from a given sample most correlates with a target ticker or index
            so that I can decide which fund to use when trading the underlying index.
        </UserStory>
        <Example>
            Technical Analysis indicates that the Home Builders industry may outperform the market.
            Using this feature, I can find the fund which best tracks a Home Builders index, which itself cannot be traded.
        </Example>
    </Feature>
    <Feature name="CSV Output - PriceHistoryCsvFile">
        <Added>23 March 2012</Added>
        <UserStory>
            As a user, I can write Price History data to CSV files.
            Output should be compatible with the existing PriceHistoryCsvFile CSV->Object logic.
        </UserStory>
    </Feature>
    <Feature name="CSV Output - TransactionHistoryCsvFile">
        <Added>23 March 2012</Added>
        <UserStory>
            As a user, I can write Transaction History data to CSV files.
            Output should be compatible with the existing TransactionHistoryCsvFile CSV->Object logic.
        </UserStory>
    </Feature>
    <Feature name="PriceRelative indicator">
        <Added>23 March 2012</Added>
        <UserStory>
            As a user, I can create an indicator to show me the relative price of two TimeSeries.
        </UserStory>
    </Feature>
    <Feature name="Trendlines">
        <Added>23 March 2012</Added>
        <UserStory>
            As a user, I can create trend lines for a TimeSeries. Trend lines will have a head and tail, and a value for each day between head and tail.
            The slope of the trendline should be observable by the user.
        </UserStory>
    </Feature>
</Features>